{
    "subject": "resource/Federal_Institute_for_Risk_Assessment",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Berlin",
    "human_readable": "The location of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment is Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9879702925682068,
            "question": "Is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment situated in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149953722953796,
            "question": "Where is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8772911429405212,
            "question": "What is the location of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8616183996200562,
            "question": "In which country is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.841847836971283,
            "question": "Where is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8354393243789673,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145055174827576,
            "question": "In which German city can you find the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7574690580368042,
            "question": "What is the address of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7249555587768555,
            "question": "To which city is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment affiliated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6871970891952515,
            "question": "What city houses the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment is Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which city is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment affiliated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the address of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which German city can you find the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2898_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason is that according to the document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2898/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt`, the location of the German Federal Institute for Risk Assessment (BfR) is indeed Berlin. The text explicitly states \"Location: Berlin - Berlin\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment (BfR) and its locations, including Berlin. Specifically, document 5.txt mentions that the BfR has a \"Berlin - Berlin\" location under the \"Location\" field, which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}